♪♪♪
♪ Snoop ♪
♪ When the pimps
in the crib ma ♪
♪ Drop it like it's hot ♪
♪ When the pigs
try to get at you ♪
♪ Park it like it's hot ♪
♪ And if a get a attitude ♪
♪ Pop it like it's hot ♪
♪ I got the Rollie on my arm
and I'm pouring Chandon ♪
♪ And I roll the best
'cause I got it going on ♪
♪ I'm a nice dude with
some nice dreams ♪
♪ See these ice cubes
see these ice creams ♪
♪ Eligible bachelor ♪
♪ Million dollar boat ♪
♪ That's whiter than
what's your throat ♪
♪ The Phantom exterior
like fish eggs ♪
♪ The interior like
wrist red ♪
♪ I can exercise you
this can be your physe ♪
♪ Cheat on your man ma
that's how you get ♪
♪ Killer with the beat I
know killers in the street ♪
♪ With the steel
that'll make you feel ♪
♪ like Chinchilla in the heat ♪
♪ So don't try to
run up on my ear ♪
♪ Talking all that raspy ♪
♪ Tryna ask me ♪
♪ When my fill they
ain't gon' pass me ♪
♪ You should think
about it take a second ♪
♪ Matter fact you
should take four B ♪
♪ And think before you fuck
with lil skateboard P ♪
♪ When the pimp's
in the crib ma ♪
♪ Drop it like it's hot ♪
♪ When the pigs
try to get at you ♪
♪ Park it like it's hot ♪
♪ And if a get a attitude ♪
♪ Pop it like it's hot ♪
♪ I got the rollie on my arm
and I'm pouring Chandon ♪
♪ And I roll the best
'cause I got it going on ♪
♪ I'm a gangsta ♪
♪ But y'all knew that ♪
♪ Da big boss dog
yeah I do that ♪
♪ I keep a flag hanging
out my backside ♪
♪ But only on the left side
Yeah that's the side ♪
♪ Ain't no other way to play
the game the way I play ♪
♪ I cut so much you
thought I was a dj ♪
♪ Two one yep three ♪
♪ S N double O P D O double G ♪
♪ I can't fake it just break
it and when I take it ♪
♪ See I specialize in making
all the girls get naked ♪
♪ So bring your friends
all of y'all come inside ♪
♪ We got a world premiere
right here now get live ♪
♪ So don't change the
dizzle turn it up a little ♪
♪ I got a living room full
of fine dime rizzles ♪
♪ Waiting on the pizzle the
dizzle and the shizzle ♪
♪ Gs to the bizzack now
ladies here we gizzo ♪
♪ When the pimp's
in the crib ma ♪
♪ Drop it like it's hot ♪
♪ When the pigs
try to get at you ♪
♪ Park it like it's hot ♪
♪ And if a get a attitude ♪
♪ Pop it like it's hot ♪
♪ I got the rollie on my arm
and I'm pouring Chandon ♪
♪ And I roll the best
'cause I got it going on ♪
♪ I'm a bad boy with a lotta ♪
♪ Drive my own cars and
wear my own clothes ♪
♪ I hang out tough ♪
♪ I'm a real boss ♪
♪ Big Snoop Dogg
yeah he's so sharp ♪
♪ On the TV screen
and in the magazines ♪
♪ If you play me
close you're on a ♪
♪ Oh you got a so
you wanna back ♪
♪ Now stop that ♪
♪ Shoes now I'm on the move ♪
♪ Your family is crying
now you on the news ♪
♪ They can't find you
and now they miss you ♪
♪ Must I remind you I'm
only here to twist you ♪
♪ Whip you dip you
then flip you ♪
♪ Then dance to
this music we to ♪
♪ Subscribe get yo' issue ♪
♪ Baby come close let me
see how you get loose ♪
♪ When the pimp's
in the crib ma ♪
♪ Drop it like it's hot ♪
♪ When the pigs
try to get at you ♪
♪ Park it like it's hot ♪
♪ And if a get a attitude ♪
♪ Pop it like it's hot ♪
♪ I got the rollie on my arm
and I'm pouring Chandon ♪
♪ And I roll the best
'cause I got it going on ♪
♪ Snoop ♪
♪♪♪